Now we're going to talk about the smallest of all of the stripes on the food pyramid, the yellow one right here which you can barely see.
That is the oils food group.
It's not technically a food group, but some oils an contribute to good health if you're getting the right ones.
Healthy oils can be found in fish, nuts, corn oil, soybean oil, olive oil, or canola oil.
Now most kids get enough of their daily intake from this category without actually having to make an effort to add things in.
The recommended daily allowance for children four to five years old is four to five teaspoons.
A teaspoon is that big.
As you can see it's not very big.
Now one teaspoon is half a tablespoon of mayo, half a tablespoon of margarine or butter, eight olives without the pits, one tablespoon of Italian salad dressing, or half an ounce of nuts.
And that's all there is for the oils group.